## **Breno Gaudereto Oliveira**

Timóteo, MG - Brazil

## **Profile**

In March, 2019, after 5 years of entrepreneurship, I decided to follow my desires of becoming a Remote Developer. I already had being studying for the last 3 years, but with my Company taking most part of my time. From March to November, I have been working in my mother's company, where I am partner, just in the afternoons, so had time to study more and start accumulate experiences in development. In December I got my first offer to work contracted in a startup of Brazil. The contract was for just 1 month, but as they liked my job, I got another contract to more 3 months, and already a little raise.

The company that I'm working now is nice, I believe in their project, and the tech team is really cool to work with, but I still intent to work for a company abroad, maybe US or Europe.

# **Employment History**

### Full Stack Developer at Kotaki Digital, São Paulo/SP (REMOTE)

December, 2019 - Present

I make features and fix bugs from the backend to the front in web or mobile. All with the stack: nodeJS, reactJS, and react-native. I am more focused on backend, where I believe e can deliver more, with more quality.

I am helping with the configuration of the infrastructure in Azure DevOps. I configured the CI/CD for most repositories like the backend server, and the 2 front end web sites. I also set a Cron in Azure Functions so the statuses update every night, and at the morning another Cron is activated to push notifications to the users that have to be alerted of something.

The database is in MySQL.

## Half Time: Full Stack Developer Student

March, 2019 - February, 2020

**Completed Courses:** 

- PHP MVC from scratch Abr/2019
- Javascript Intermediate Mai/2019
- Javascript Advanced Mai/2019
- Full NodeJS Mai/2019
- Express Optimization of NodeJS applications Jun/2019
- Semana OmniStack 7.0 da RocketSeat (no certification) Jun/2019
- React Introduction Jul/2019
- React Redux e Redux Saga Jul/2019
- React Mastering Components Jul/2019
- React Advanced Topics Jul/2019
- Semana OmniStack 8.0 da RocketSeat (no certification) Ago/2019
- Scrum Planning and Agile Development out/2019

Beyond the projects developed in these courses, I have my own projects, that can be seen in my portfolio: <a href="https://brenogo.tech">https://brenogo.tech</a>.

### Half Time: Minority Partner at Agito Boutique, Timóteo/MG

March, 2019 - February, 2020

Contribute with administrations processes such as admissions, demissions, payment, financial control, bills and all that affects the administration of the company.

#### Managing Partner at Rolf Modas, Rio Pomba/MG

January, 2014 - January, 2019

Responsible of everything of the company. There I started to learn web development and created our online ERP.

### Operations Analytics at América Latina Logística, Bauru/SP

January, 2014 - January, 2019

I was responsible for the mechanised maintenance of the company's rail roads in the states of São Paulo, Mato Grosso and Mato Grosso do Sul.

### **Education**

## Industrial Engineering, Viçosa Federal University

January, 2007 - January, 2012

Beyond the whole engineering classes, I also had Algorithm and Programming Introduction, where I had my first contact with programming, with C++.